Inventory of the Aerial Photographs
The University Library
Aerial photographs
1958-1965
MS 263
Santa Cruz County Advertising Committee
1 flat
University of California, Santa Cruz. University Library. Special Collections and Archives Santa Cruz, California 95064
This collection contains thirteen aerial photographs of Seacliff, Watsonville, Pajaro Valley, Cabrillo College and Ben Lomond areas taken for the Santa Cruz County Advertising Committee.
Access
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Warren Littlefield
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection contains thirteen aerial photographs of Seacliff, Watsonville, Pajaro Valley, Cabrillo College and Ben Lomond areas taken for the Santa Cruz County Advertising Committee.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Santa Cruz County Advertising Committee; Santa Cruz County (Calif.)--Aerial photographs
Container List
- Seacliff #C226-2, March 23, 1963 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Watsonville - Pajaro Valley, March 23, 1963 (Box-folder 1:2-3)
  - #C227-1, March 23, 1963 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - #C227-2, March 23, 1963 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Pajaro Valley #C227-3, March 23, 1963 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Cabrillo College area, May 3, 1965 (Box-folder 1:5-7)
  - #C964-1, May 3, 1965 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - #C964-2, May 3, 1965 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - #C964-3, May 3, 1965 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Watsonville, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:8-10)
  - #KA-197, March 27, 1958 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - #KA-263, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - #KA-282-2, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Watsonville - Pajaro River #KA-285, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:11)
- Ben Lomond #KA-289-1, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Ben Lomond #KA-290, ca. 1958 (Box-folder 1:13)